protank.com 2007-06-12

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy summarizes how We collect information from you and how WE may use it. By using this Website, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to the use of your information in accordance with this Policy. If you do not agree our Policy, please do not use our Website.

 **Information Collected**

WE collect general information provided by your internet connected computer to better understand user demographics, to improve our Website and to better meet your needs; such as the type of browser that you use, the services and products you requested, the domain name and country from which you request information, the Website that you just came from, and the Website you next visit and your IP address.

 **Uses and Disclosure of Information Collected**

WE will not release or use your personal information without your consent, except as specified in this Privacy Policy.

The information that you supply will be used to respond to your inquiries, to provide you with products and services, and to monitor transactions that you carry out with us. WE may authorize third party suppliers and service providers to use this information solely to assist us in providing our products and services.

WE may use your information to contact you about any new or updated products and services. WE may offer optional questionnaires, surveys and other information to you to assess and meet your interests and needs. The use of the information collected in questionnaires and surveys will be explained in such questionnaires and surveys. You will be able to "unsubscribe" to such information mailings and contacts at any time.

WE may share aggregate information about our users with advertisers, business partners, and other third parties, but such information will not personally identify any individual.

If you terminate your account or deactivate specific services, WE will maintain some basic information about you in association with these services, including your name and address. This information will only be used by us for internal record keeping purposes, as required by law or as otherwise permitted by you. Upon any termination of your account, WE will also retain general information about you which does not identify you personally, but which may still be included with our aggregate information that is provided to third parties. Information that you provide to us can never be completely removed from databases due to technical constraints and the fact that WE back up our systems.

WE may disclose your information in special cases when WE have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, its users, or anyone else, WE may also disclose your information when WE believe in good faith that the law requires it.

**Cookies**

Like most Websites, WE may use cookies to keep track of your purchases and other activity on the Website and enhance your experience on the Website. WE may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. Third party advertisers on the Website may also place cookies on your browser. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas on the Website

**Links to Other Websites**

Our Website may contain links to other Websites, including Websites of affiliated companies. WE do not endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those Websites. You should carefully review the privacy statements and other terms of use for such Websites. These other Websites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

WE reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and WE will promptly include any modifications within the online version of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Website after any modifications are posted to the Website shall constitute your acceptance of all such modifications. The date of the most recent revision is shown at the bottom of this page.

**Security of Information Cannot be guaranteed**

WE strive to protect our user's personal information and privacy. WE cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and therefore you do so at your own risk. If you use this Website, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account and password and for restricting access to your computer.
